{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Quiz1.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "In cucina c'e' il tavolo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485055.9542441,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In the kitchen there is the table.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "I am",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485020.5804205,
            "question": "Given the definition \"io sono\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "my name is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453484895.0893638,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"mi chiamo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lei di dov'e?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485027.0963845,
            "question": "Where are you from? (formal)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Piacere di conoscerLa.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485094.5183537,
            "question": "Pleased to meet you. (formal)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Here are my friends.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485014.8264177,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ecco i miei amici.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Ecco i miei amici.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485042.7191436,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Here are my friends.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "tu sei",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485059.6887796,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you are (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "mi chiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485147.155893,
            "question": "Given the definition \"my name is\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "noi siamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485141.6087306,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"we are\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "rosse",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485158.8917828,
            "question": "Le sedie sono (red)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "C'e' il fratello.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485196.5719697,
            "question": "Given the definition \"There's the brother.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "y'all are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485105.506656,
            "question": "Given the definition \"voi siete\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "In the kitchen there is the table.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485137.2453542,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In cucina c'e' il tavolo.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "io sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485099.1123426,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "loro sono",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453485212.9046364,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"they are\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "we are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485289.760055,
            "question": "Given the definition \"noi siamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "your apartment",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485306.1498532,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il tuo appartamento\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "voi siete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485248.6279273,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"y'all are\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "There's the brother.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485283.8066182,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"C'e' il fratello.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "you are (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485243.9401758,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tu sei\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "il tuo appartamento",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485312.2907994,
            "question": "Given the definition \"your apartment\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "they are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485293.8540182,
            "question": "Given the definition \"loro sono\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Come sta?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485300.9960568,
            "question": "How are you? (formal)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "she/he is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485320.3380716,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lei/lui e'\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "grande",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485337.3209567,
            "question": "L'appartamento di Maria e' (big)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Prego.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485384.8848646,
            "question": "You're welcome.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "intelligente",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485389.1975532,
            "question": "Tua cugina e' (intelligent)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "gialli",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485342.590155,
            "question": "I cuscini sono (yellow)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "(Io) sono di Boston.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485328.0927336,
            "question": "I'm from Boston.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "lei/lui e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453485369.1468928,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"she/he is\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "simpatica",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453485395.0103917,
            "question": "Mia sorella e' (nice)",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}